

CONTACT

- +8801745547332
- milon.hossain8152@gmail.com
- Trishal Namapara, Mymensingh, 2220
 - https://www.facebook.com/milon.mahmmud.5/

EDUCATION

2023 - 24

Jatiya Kabi Kazi Nazrul Islam University

- Master of Social Science
- Population Science
- On-going

2018 - 24

Jatiya Kabi Kazi Nazrul Islam University

- Bachelor of Social Science
- Population Science
- CGPA: 3.59 / 4.00

SKILLS

- Data collection
- Data analysis
- Report writing
- STATA
- SPSS
- Project Management
- Teamwork
- Collaboration
- Time Management

LANGUAGES

- Bangla (Fluent)
- English (Intermediate)

MD. MILON HOSSAIN

Research Assistance | Data Collector | Data Analysist

Profile

Enthusiastic public health research assistance with over 1 year experience. Expertise in developing research tools, data collection, data management, data analysis with proven skills in report writing & project handling. Keen to utilize my skills to contribute to meaningful research project.

Work Experience

Research Assistance

2023 - 24

Jatiya Kabi Kazi Nazrul Islam University Research and Extension Center's Funded Project

- Title "The Impact of Climate Change on Sexual and Reproductive Health"
- Collaborating on a team to conduct a large-scale research study.
- Developing research tools.
- Data collection.
- Compiling, transcribing and analyzing data.
- Assisting in report writing

Research Intern

Oct. 2024 - Dec. 2024

SAVE (Service and Vision for Edity)

- Conducting in-depth interviews and focus group discussion.
- Developing research tools.
- Data collection.
- Compiled, transcribed and analyzed qualitative data.
- Assisted in report writing.
- Assisting in report writing

ACHIEVEMENT

2023 - 2024

Honours Project

 Title "Prevalence and Factors Associated with Antenatal Care Visits among Female Ready-Made Garment Workers in Bangladesh: Insights from a Cross-Sectional Study

REFERENCE

Md. Syful Islam

Assistant Professor, Jatiya Kabi Kazi Nazrul Islam University, Trishal, Mymensingh.

Mobile: 01854-948713 Email: syful111@gmail.com

Md. Kabir Hossain

Lecturer,

Abdulpur Govt. College, Natore, Rajshahi.

Mobile: 01759-122919

Email: kabir8th@gmail.com